A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 300 Latin America - Series 833 Lebanon FA387b
Rockefeller Archive Center
- North Africa Region, 1946-1964; 485; 4 box(es)
  - North Africa Region - Humanities and Arts, 485.R
    - Mones, Hussein, 1950-1953, 1956, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Musical Survey, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - North Africa Region - Social Sciences, 485.S
    - American University at Cairo - Population Study, 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - American University at Cairo - Rizk, Hanna, 1950-1951, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Libya - Foreign Affairs - Books, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Morocco - Foreign Affairs - Books, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Sudan - Foreign Affairs - Books, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Tunisia - Foreign Affairs - Books, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - University of Khartoum - Social Services, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- South Africa Region, 1929-1971; 487; 6 box(es)
  Six subseries as follows: 487 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 487 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 487 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 487 R Humanities and arts 487 S Social sciences 487 V Virus studies
  - South Africa Region - General (No Program), 487.GEN
    - Institute of Family and Community Health - Cohn, Helen Dorothy, 1949, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Poliomyelitis Research Foundation Laboratories - Winter, P.A.D., 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - South African Institute for Medical Research - De Meillon, Botha, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Virus Diseases, 1950, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 4-9)
    - Virus Diseases - Administration, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
    - Virus Diseases - Administration - Supplementary Material, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Weinbren, M.P., 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - South Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 487.A
    - Gear, Harry Sutherland, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - South Africa - Medical and Nursing Education, 1929, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Tobias, Phillip V., 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland - Morris, Richard Murchison, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - University of CapeTown - Hansen, John D.L., 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - University of Natal - Family Practice, 1953-1961 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
    - University of Natal - Family Practice - Supplementary Reports, 1956-1959 (Box 3, Folder 21-23)
    - University of Natal - Gillman, Theodore, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - University of Natal - Medical School, 1949-1955 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - University of Natal - Pathology, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - University of Witwatersrand - Stein, H.B., 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - South Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 487.D
    - Domboshawa School - Library, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland - Agriculture, 1958-1968 (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
    - University of Pretoria - Joffe, A., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - University of Pretoria - Plant Physiology, 1947-1958 (Box 4, Folder 32-33)
    - University of Witwatersrand - Badenhuizen, N.P., 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - South Africa Region - Humanities and Arts, 487.R
    - Rhodes-Livingstone Institute - Rotberg, Robert, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - South Africa Region - Social Sciences, 487.S
    - Botswana - External Affairs - Books, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Council of Education, Witwatersrand, 1953-1955, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Lesotho - Foreign Affairs - Books, 1967, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Rhodes-Livingstone Institute, 1958-1961 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Rhodes-Livingstone Institute - Supplementary Material, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Rhodesia and Nyasaland - External Affairs - Books, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Swaziland - Foreign Affairs - Books, 1967, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland - African Economic Behavior, 1958-1962, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland - Library, 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland - McIntosh, Bruce Merton, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - South Africa Region - Virus Studies, 487.V
    - Virus Diseases, 1958-1964 (Box 5, Folder 46-51)
    - Virus Diseases - Administration, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Virus Diseases - Administration, 1959-1964 (Box 6, Folder 53-54)
    - Virus Diseases - Annual Reports, 1954-1959 (Box 6, Folder 55-60)
    - Virus Diseases - Reprint, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Uganda, 1958-1975; 492; 12 box(es)
  Eight subseries as follows: 492 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 492 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 492 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 492 E Fellowships, scholarships, training awards 492 R Humanities and arts 492 S Social sciences 492 V Virus studies 492 W Schistosomiasis
  - Uganda - General (No Program), 492.GEN
    - Lincoln School, Kampala, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Makerere College - African Staff, 1962-1964, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Makerere College - African Studies, 1962-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
    - Makerere College - African Studies - Supplementary Material, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
    - Makerere College - Library, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
    - Makerere College - Lule, Y.K., 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Makerere College - Viesel, Helmut, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Uganda - Medical Sciences, 492.A
    - Health - Kiboneka, Gad Harold, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Makerere College - Allbrook, David, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Makerere College - Bilharziasis, 1961-1966, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Makerere College - Biochemistry, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Makerere College - Galloway, Alexander, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Makerere College - Graduate Training, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Makerere College - Jelliffe, Derrick Brian, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Makerere College - Lunn, H. Fletcher, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Makerere College - Lutwama, Joseph S.W., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Makerere College - Medical Training, 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Makerere College - Preventive Medicine, 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 23-25)
    - Makerere College - Preventive Medicine, 1965-1968, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
    - Makerere College - Reproductive Biology, 1966-1969, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Makerere College - Trussell, Richard R., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Uganda - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 492.D
    - Empire Cotton Growing Corporation - Le Mare, Peter H., 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Makerere College - Agricultural Conference, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Makerere College - Agricultural Conference - Proceedings, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
    - Makerere College - Barlow, E.S.H., 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Makerere College - Beadle, L.C., 1960 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Makerere College - Boshoff, Willem Hendrik, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Makerere College - Ddungu, John, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Makerere College - Ghosh, Biswa Nath, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Makerere College - Guest House, 1960-1961, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Makerere College - Holliday, Robert, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Makerere College - Kiwuwa, Gabriel Hamlin, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Makerere College - MacDonald, Andrew Sinclair, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Makerere College - Mahadevan, Pararajasingham, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Makerere College - Musangi, Richard S., 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Makerere College - Oland, Kristian, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Makerere College - Parish, Denis Hedley, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Makerere College - Soil Nematology, 1960-1964, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Makerere College - Wilson, Fergus, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Mugera, John S., 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Uganda - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 492.E
    - Akiki-Mujaju, Ephraim Bomera, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 50-51)
    - Alibaruho, George, 1967-1975 (Box 4, Folder 52-53)
    - Ezeife, Chukuemeka P., 1968-1973 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Gingyera-Pinjcwa, Anthony C.G., 1963-1972 (Box 4, Folder 55-56)
    - Kabushenga, Hilda M., 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Kabwegyere, Tarsisio B., 1967-1973 (Box 5, Folder 58-59)
    - Kiwuwa, Gabriel A., 1968-1973 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Kyegombe, David Benjamin, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Mugerwa, Joshua Wamala, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Mukuru, Samwiri Ziryabareba, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Musoke, Theresa, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Nanji, Azim Akberali, 1967-1972 (Box 6, Folder 65-66)
    - Ongom, Virginio Lachara, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Zake, Julius Y.K., 1967-1972 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Uganda - Humanities and Arts, 492.R
    - Makerere College - African Music, 1961-1969 (Box 6, Folder 69-70)
    - Makerere College - Creative Writing, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Makerere College - Drama, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Makerere College - History, 1960-1963, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Makerere College - History Exchange, 1968-1972 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Makerere College - Linguistics - Grannis, Oliver C., 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Makerere College - Mensah, A.A., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Makerere College - Religion, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 77-78)
    - National Theatre, 1960-1966 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Uganda Museum, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Uganda - Social Sciences, 492.S
    - East African Institute of Social Research - Industrialization, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - External Relations - Books, 1962-1963, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Makerere College - Administrative Training, 1961-1964, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Makerere College - Barot, Rohit, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Makerere College - Economic Research, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 85-86)
    - Makerere College - Economic Research, 1964-1971 (Box 8, Folder 87-92)
    - Makerere College - Economic Research - Workshops, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Makerere College - Economics, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Makerere College - Economics, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 95-96)
    - Makerere College - Economics - Clower, Robert W., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Makerere College - Economics - Dawson, John C., 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Makerere College - Economics - Falkus, Malcom Edward, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Makerere College - Economics - Haskell, Mark A., 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Makerere College - Ekpebu, Lawrence, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Makerere College - Ezeife, Chukuemeka P., 1967 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Makerere College - International Relations, 1961-1966, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 103-105)
    - Makerere College - International Relations - Edmondson, Locksley G.E., 1966, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Makerere College - Leys, Colin, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Makerere College - Mazrui, Ali A., 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Makerere College - Political Science, 1962-1968 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Makerere College - Political Science - Abdel-Rahim, Muddathir, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Makerere College - Political Science - Conference, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Makerere College - Political Science - Grundy, Kenneth W., 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Makerere College - Political Science - Kasfir, Nelson M., 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Makerere College - Political Science - Research, 1965-1970 (Box 10, Folder 114-116)
    - Makerere College - Rigby, Peter John Arthur, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Makerere College - Social Sciences - Teaching Assistants, 1966-1970, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Makerere College - Sociology, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - Makerere College - Wandira, Asavia, 1969,1971 (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Makerere University - Administrator's Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Makerere University - Development Policy, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - Makerere University - Economics - Csapo, Laszlo, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - Makerere University - Economics - Hall, Marshall, 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Makerere University - Muwonge, Joseph W., 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - Makerere University - Political Science - Ryan, Selwyn Douglas, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Makerere University - Public Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Makerere University - Sociology - Artis, Jay W., 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Makerere University - Sociology - Mushanga, Musa T., 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - Uganda - Virus Studies, 492.V
    - Virus Research Institute, Entebbe - Ellice, James M., 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 130)
    - Virus Research Institute, Entebbe - Kafuko, George William, 1966-1968 (Box 12, Folder 131)
    - Virus Research Institute, Entebbe - Williams, Miles, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 132)
    - Virus Research Institute, Entebbe - Woodall, John P., 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Uganda - Schistosomiasis, 492.W
    - Makerere College - Bradley, David J., 1966-1970 (Box 12, Folder 134)
- Sudan, 1958-1977; 494; 8 box(es)
  Six subseries as follows: 494 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 494 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 494 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 494 E Fellowships, scholarships, training awards 494 R Humanities and arts 494 S Social sciences
  - Sudan - General (No Program), 494.GEN
    - University of Khartoum, 1961-1968, 1971, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1-8)
    - University of Khartoum - A-Z, 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - University of Khartoum - Agriculture, 1962-1967 (Box 2, Folder 10-12)
    - University of Khartoum - Arid Lands, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - University of Khartoum - Arid Lands - Supplementary Material, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - University of Khartoum - Arid Lands - Supplementary Material, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    - University of Khartoum - Dafaalla, El Nazeer, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - University of Khartoum - Extramural Studies - Halim, Ahmad Abdal, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - University of Khartoum - Hasan, Yusuf Fadl, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - University of Khartoum - Hassan, Mohamed Ahmed, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - University of Khartoum - Home Economics - McNiel, Bessie, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - University of Khartoum - Library, 1961-1968 (Box 3, Folder 22-25)
    - University of Khartoum - Neil, Hamad El (Hamad El Neil Abdel Rahman), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - University of Khartoum - Osman, Abdel Hamid, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - University of Khartoum - Osman, Abdel Hamid El Sayed, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 28-29)
    - University of Khartoum - Statistics, 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - University of Khartoum - Sudan Unit, 1962-1967 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - University of Khartoum - Supplementary Material, 1961-1962, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 32-33)
    - University of Khartoum - Whiteman, Arthur J., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Sudan - Medical Sciences, 494.A
    - University of Khartoum - Haseeb, Mansouri Ali, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - University of Khartoum - Khogali, Ali, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - University of Khartoum - Medical School, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - University of Khartoum - Medical School, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - University of Khartoum - Mustafa, Donald, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Sudan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 494.D
    - Church Missionary Society, Yei - Carr, Stephan J., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - University of Khartoum - Abbadi, Saad Ahmed Beshir, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - University of Khartoum - Agabawi, Kamal Abdalla, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - University of Khartoum - Agriculture, 1958-1966 (Box 5, Folder 43-46)
    - University of Khartoum - Agriculture - Nour, El Imam El Khidir Mohammed, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - University of Khartoum - Ayed, Ibrahim Abdulla, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - University of Khartoum - Bannaga, Ali Mahayad, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - University of Khartoum - Bayoumi, M.S., 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - University of Khartoum - Cloudsley-Thompson, J.L., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - University of Khartoum - Coleman, Francis, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - University of Khartoum - Ecology, 1966-1968, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - University of Khartoum - Hassan Ishag, Mustafa, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - University of Khartoum - Horticulture - Abdalla, Abdalla Ahmed, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - University of Khartoum - Kambal, Ali E., 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - University of Khartoum - Kanagasuntheram, R., 1961-1962, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - University of Khartoum - Khan, Abdul Quddus, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - University of Khartoum - Khatim, Sam Ibrahim El, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - University of Khartoum - Khattab, Abdel Gadir Hassan, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - University of Khartoum - Kheir, Ali M., 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - University of Khartoum - Mamoun, Izzel Din Mohammad, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - University of Khartoum - Mustafa, Ibrahim El Disougi, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - University of Khartoum - Nasri, Mohamed El, 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - University of Khartoum - Nour, Mohamed A., 1961, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - University of Khartoum - Primates, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - University of Khartoum - Saeed, E.A.K. El, 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - University of Khartoum - Shazali, Mohamed (Osman), 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - University of Khartoum - Sineina, Mohamed El Amin Abu, 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - University of Khartoum - Venkatraman, Tarakkad Venkitakrishna, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Sudan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 494.E
    - Khalifa, Mohamed Ahmed, 1967-1972 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Sudan - Humanities and Arts, 494.R
    - University of Khartoum - French Language Program, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - University of Khartoum - Language Research, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - University of Khartoum - Library - Bindery Program, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - University of Khartoum - Library - Nasri, Abdel Rahman El, 1961-1962, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - University of Khartoum - Philosophy, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - University of Khartoum - Shibeika, Mekki, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Sudan - Social Sciences, 494.S
    - Institute of Public Administration - Research Methodology Training, 1963-1964, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - University of Khartoum - Agib, Abdel Rahman Ahmed El, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - University of Khartoum - Ahmad Syed, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - University of Khartoum - Geography, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - University of Khartoum - Henin, Roushdi A., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - University of Khartoum - Osman, Omar Mohamed, 1962-1967 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - University of Khartoum - Political Science, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 84-86)
    - University of Khartoum - Political Science, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - University of Khartoum - Political Science - Lectures, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - University of Khartoum - Suliman, Ali Ahmed, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - University of Khartoum - Thornton, Douglas S., 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 90)
- West Africa Region, 1950-1972; 495; 5 box(es)
  Six subseries as follows: 495 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 495 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 495 C Nursing (nursing education, public health nursing) 495 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 495 R Humanities and arts 495 S Social sciences
  - West Africa Region - General (No Program), 495.GEN
    - Adwei, Eustace A., 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Eddey, Leslie George, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Education, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Fabiyi, Akinyele, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Lovanium University - Ronsse, C.S., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - West African Science Association - Conference, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - West Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 495.A
    - Ghana - Health - Charles, L.J., 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Liberian Institute, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Liberian Institute - Supplementary Material - Annual Reports, 1955, 1957, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Liberian Institute - Supplementary Material - Reprints, 1955-1956, 1958-1959, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Lovanium University, 1955-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11-15)
    - Lovanium University - Histophotometer, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Lovanium University - Supplementary Material - Reprints, 1950-1951, 1955-1957, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - University College, Ibadan - Cardiovascular Research, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - University College, Ibadan - Grayson, John, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - University College, Ibadan - Pediatrics, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - University College, Ibadan - Pediatrics, 1960-1968, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 21-23)
    - University College, Ibadan - Pediatrics - Supplementary Material, 1961, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 24-26)
    - University College, Ibadan - Visits, 1952-1959 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - West Africa Region - Nursing, 495.C
    - Lovanium University, 1956, 1958-1963 (Box 3, Folder 28-30)
  - West Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 495.D
    - Anthony, Frank S., 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Chinwuba, Patrick M., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Kolo Agronomy Station, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Lovanium University, 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Lovanium University - Peeters, Gerard, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Pin Pino, John A. Diary of a Trip to Senegal, Mali, Upper Volta, Ivory Coast, Nigeria, and Uganda, August 4-24, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Saria Agricultural Station, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - University College, Ibadan - Agriculture, 1958-1962, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - University College, Ibadan - Udom, George Essien, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Wortman, Sterling L. - Diary of a Trip to French West Africa, August 15-28, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - West Africa Region - Humanities and Arts, 495.R
    - University College, Ibadan - Arabic and Islamic Studies, 1959-1967 (Box 4, Folder 41-44)
    - University College, Ibadan - Drama, 1959-1962 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - University College, Ibadan - Press, 1958, 1960-1962, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 46)